<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz Media]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz Media]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/nick-kalisz-media/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 14:34:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/nick-kalisz-media/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel // 2015]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel // 2015</h1><p>This is my story from the past year of beauty and joy, leading into some of the hardships we all encounter. As in any life these hardships can lead to great success. Nick Kalisz' film career is inspired by the great outdoors and the raw beauty of human emotion.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/134061360</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b16dfcdd-69aa-4f9d-9f98-c901bdbbd10e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 14:34:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel</h1><p>This is my story from the past year of beauty and joy, leading into some of the hardships we all encounter. As in any life these hardships can lead to great success.
Nick Kalisz’ film career is inspired by the great outdoors and the raw beauty of human emotion.
After graduating from Ohio University’s Scripps School of Communication in Film and Video Production Nick migrated to Jackson Hole, Wyoming. He quickly realized his passion for capturing human interaction in nature. As a former athlete, Nick's unique ability to travel quickly, efficiently and safely in high alpine terrain has led him to film production around the world. From the Austrian Alps and high Himalayas of Nepal to remote Alaska and Mt. Kilimanjaro Nick has filmed commercials, television, major motion pictures and sports documentaries. Nick has unique talent and passion for operating premier production gear, implementing hollywood techniques, managing media and running equipment on solar in some of the most remote and harsh backcountry locations in the world.
Equipment: 4k Red Digital Cinema Cameras, Phantom Camera Systems, Canon, Sony, DJI Inspire, DJI Ronin, Feather Light Camera Crane, Kessler Products and Programing, Adobe Creative Suite.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d8dc87766c4ebf2cecbc04a6f82d1a7610b2cbd6.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5483b985-c249-4a87-b9b4-3f5b53ce21a9.png</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ff715a7c-9d1e-46bd-ae51-e966835877cd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>