<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz Media]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz Media]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/nick-kalisz-media/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:01:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/nick-kalisz-media/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Nick Kalisz // Demo Reel</h1><p>This is my story from the past year of beauty and joy, leading into some of the hardships we all encounter. As in any life these hardships can lead to great success.
Nick Kalisz’ film career is inspired by the great outdoors and the raw beauty of human emotion.
After graduating from Ohio University’s Scripps School of Communication in Film and Video Production Nick migrated to Jackson Hole, Wyoming. He quickly realized his passion for capturing human interaction in nature. As a former athlete, Nick's unique ability to travel quickly, efficiently and safely in high alpine terrain has led him to film production around the world. From the Austrian Alps and high Himalayas of Nepal to remote Alaska and Mt. Kilimanjaro Nick has filmed commercials, television, major motion pictures and sports documentaries. Nick has unique talent and passion for operating premier production gear, implementing hollywood techniques, managing media and running equipment on solar in some of the most remote and harsh backcountry locations in the world.
Equipment: 4k Red Digital Cinema Cameras, Phantom Camera Systems, Canon, Sony, DJI Inspire, DJI Ronin, Feather Light Camera Crane, Kessler Products and Programing, Adobe Creative Suite.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d8dc87766c4ebf2cecbc04a6f82d1a7610b2cbd6.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5483b985-c249-4a87-b9b4-3f5b53ce21a9.png</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ff715a7c-9d1e-46bd-ae51-e966835877cd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Beautiful Speedometer for Bikes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Beautiful Speedometer for Bikes</h1><p>Shout-out to designers who are also obsessed with cycling because their work frequently results in something new and clever, like the arresting Omata One. Mounted onto a bike, the speedometer's unique analog face informs of the four most relevant ride metrics (speed, distance, ascent and time).</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d105236023603a813c26d257fbe058ad72b3f663.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/tech/omata-one-analog-gps-speedometer-cycling-kickstarter</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6b14c564-c4fa-4276-971f-8be831ebefc9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 21:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Disney space station? It no longer seems like such a goofy idea]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Disney space station? It no longer seems like such a goofy idea</h1><p>Throughout our planet's space-faring history, there have been two major impediments to putting a lot of private citizens into orbit. Only governments have had spacecraft, and there have been only a few, government-controlled, space stations to visit. But now that may finally changing in a big way.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d83d67a7d53a5e25e15266ea03dab94cba53ee33.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://arstechnica.com/science/2016/04/a-disney-space-station-it-no-longer-seems-like-such-a-goofy-idea/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">739996bc-95d8-4ccf-a157-b86ac9ae9ad1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 21:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Science Fiction to Reality: The Evolution of Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>From Science Fiction to Reality: The Evolution of Artificial Intelligence</h1><p>What was once just a figment of the imagination of some our most famous science fiction writers, artificial intelligence (AI) is taking root in our everyday lives. We're still a few years away from having robots at our beck and call, but AI has already had a profound impact in more subtle ways.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/357196ae30863a53e7710f55ebbdd64acab6cdce.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.wired.com/insights/2015/01/the-evolution-of-artificial-intelligence/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ddfccc50-79be-427d-b5e2-194c60647546</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 21:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>